You wake up
Leave me alone
Yeah，like that'
s gonna happen
Now get up
We can still do
this the easy way
Come on
this isn't a hotel
Don't touch me
How dare you？
Do you have any
idea who I am？
Alright
here's all the
stuff you came in with
If everything
's in order
you can sign here
Miss Heine Mon
I don't ever want
to see you tossed in the cooler again
Passing out drunk
alone in a dark alley
Be thankful something horrible didn't happen to you
You got a
cigarette？
Huh？
I'm just asking
if you've got a cigarette
There's no
smoking in the station
Go outside if
you want to smoke
Lighter
Where's
my lighter？
My bag
I wanna know what
you did with my bag
And I already
told you it's the only bag you had
You liar
I know you're not
telling me the truth
I had another
shoulder bag
where is it？
Probably with
whoever stole it from you
When you passed
out drunk in the alley
What are you
going to do about it？
I had valuables
important
things in there
I'll tell you what
You can fill out
a theft report if you like
But I really
wouldn't get your hopes up
How the hell did
you lose your keys？
My bag was
stolen last night
Just hurry up and
open the room for me
What…
what
happened here？
Damn
somebody
really went to town
Oh，man
this is awful
I gotta
change the lock now
Which reminds me
Miss Heinemann
you still owe
me back rent
I don't want to
have to ask you again
The deposit you
put down has already run out
I'm gonna need
the rest of what you owe soon
These people even
broke into my damn suitcase
Are you listening？
You have to pay
for a new lock and all that back rent
Well，I don't
have any money
What？
Fine，I'll get out
don't worry
Such a
tragic story
But still
I don't know what
you expect me to do about any of it
You know
I seem to remember you being the one who stormed out on me
Oh，come on
that's all
ancient history now
So，why not
buy me a drink？
Please， Ava
That's just a
stolen purse
for God's sake
You must have had
some extra cash tucked away somewhere
Honestly
I've yet to
meet another woman
who could burn
through money the way you do
And here you are
finally coming to me for some cash
This is it
welcome to
rock bottom
baby
So，how much？
Huh？
I'll
sleep with you
you know
I'm asking you
how much you'd be willing to pay
My God
Honey
as a general rule
most men won't
pay to have sex
with women they'
ve already had a bunch of times
You can at
least buy me a drink
Go find yourself
a street corner to work
Who knows
you might get
lucky and meet some sad sack
who's not
too picky
Desperate
middleaged and
drunk must be someone's type
Yeah
I'm positive you
didn't leave any purse here last night
Maybe you left it
wherever you went next
I don't remember
anything after I left this bar
You mentioned you
had something important in your bag
If it's
worth any money
you might as
well kiss it goodbye
No，it's not
it's not worth
anything at all
Not any money
that is
Hey
I've been
looking for you
I asked for you
at the pub back there
And they told me
you just headed in this direction
Yeah，and
who are you？
Are you serious？
We had such a
good time drinking last night
I was drinking with you？
Your bag
That's why I was
looking for you
I guess this
means I have to make
awkward
introductions again？
I'm Roberto
So
shall we grab a
little something to eat？
Your hotel room？
Really？
That's terrible
I'm so sorry
Well，whatever
I mean，it's not
like you did it
Well，no
obviously not
I didn't even
dare look in your bag
Oh，look
my hotel keys
are still in here
A little
late for those
I don't need
them anymore
I'm sorry
it's all my fault
If I'd returned
your bag sooner
You wouldn't have
been kicked out of your room in the first place
Hey，it wasn't
your fault at all
Besides
I'm very grateful
that you gave me back my bag
Honestly
I'm kind of
grateful that you lost it
Well
last night as I
watched you leave the pub
I sat there
thinking to myself
You shouldn't let
this person slip away
And now
thanks to your bag
here you are
and here I am
You have something very important in there
don't you？
I do
This is all that
I have left in the world
係相簿？
May I take a look？
You may
That's my father
He looks just
like I imagined
He was a
hospital director，right？
Yeah
did I talk about
him last night？
You did
you spoke very
highly of him
You mentioned
that he died ten years ago
I could tell that
you still miss him
Let's see，ah
the exfiance？
Please
don't tell me I
told you about him
I believe his
name was Tenma？
Quite a guy
this Tenma
I really wanna
know what I said last night
Well，I wouldn't
make a habit of it
It might end up
making other men jealous
Huh？
Odd，this
page is empty
Is that so？
The photos that
were on this page
looks like
somebody tore them out
Well
I guess I didn't
need those pictures anymore
So I see
Hey
Let's get a drink
Sounds good
So
you were running
a security company？
I'm impressed
Yeah
in the
south of France
And then we
had a bad day
and one of our
better clients was killed on my watch
So，that was
the end of that
We're both going
through tough times
Nah，forget it
let's drink to
the here and now
Enjoy ourselves
you know？
Mhm
Uh
That song？
It's good stuff
huh？
So you like
this song too？
Of course
Let's dance
Come on
Well
I don't really
know how to dance
Just put your
arms around me
Um…
Good
I knew a man who
loved this song
He wasn't a very
good dancer either
So
you'd end up
dancing like this？
That's right
How fun
How about
another drink？
Just one more？
Thanks
but I'm good
Lightweight
Time for bed
Sounds good to me
babe
Those photographs
you took out of the album
Where'd you
hide them？
Tell me，You see
I'm onto your
little secret
You're
looking for Tenma
aren't you？
I know you kept
those photos from burning
And I'm sure you
have them with you somewhere
What？
You're saying
you know
where Tenma is？
Yeah
The photographs
that you're talking about
They're the ones
with father and that boy
am I right？
Johan，wasn't it？
I've seen him
you know
Blonde，charming
handsome
He's grown up well
我見過佢，一年前在杜塞爾多夫
Kenzo
Let's start over
You…
You need me
Kenzo
You belong to me
I will
get you back
Because
you're mine
So
what are you up
to these days？
I've heard all
sorts of rumours
The rumours
are probably true
I've been married
and divorced three times now
Between my father'
s inheritance and my alimony
I'm living
pretty comfortably
But enough about me
how has life
been treating you
Dr， Becker？
I dunno
nothing's
changed with me
I still have no
chance of moving up in the world
Speaking of which
Tenma's now
chief of surgery
Word is he's on
his way to becoming hospital director
Love to be
in his shoes
let me tell you
But please
who am I kidding？
It ain't so bad
I still manage to
have a good time
There's more to
life than promotions
I'd never want
to be like Tenma
and have no time
for women or fun
What's the point？
Is Kenzo…
Do you know by any chance if Doctor Tenma ever did settle down？
No，not yet
and to be
completely honest
I've introduced
him to quite a few very nice women
But you know him
no interest at all
his work
comes first
As a
matter of fact
I'm about to set
him up with a new girl
God only knows if
it's gonna work out
She's the
daughter of a state senator
and she is
absolutely beautiful
If she can't
keep his attention
then I give up
But，anyway
you called me
about something
How can I
be of service
Ava？
You know
back when you were the daughter of the hospital director
You never even
gave me the time of day
Who would have
thought that you'd even think to call？
I understand
you're well off
But really
I think you're
getting lonely
aren't you？
I mean it
when I say it，Eva
I'm more than
happy to listen
anytime
Look
I don't want you
to let them meet up
Dr Tenma and the
state senator's daughter
Don't let
him meet her
Man
I should
have known
You're still
in love with him
Don't let him…
Do me a favour
don't screw
it up this time
I went out of my
way to set this one up for you
Tenma
Well，we'll
see about that
This is it
This is the clock
that Mr， Yunker's was talking about at the hospital
Excuse me
about the clock
你已經遲到
喂，what's going on？
That's a very
beautiful watch
Oh，Why，thank you
I mean
I wear a watch
but mine
is nothing
a trinket
Honestly
I don't even
check the time anymore
I wonder why
Time seems to be
moving faster and faster
Um，excuse me，but…
who are you？
I'm sorry
I don't
mean to be rude
But are you
Senator Burger's daughter
Angelica？
Yes？
Goodness
you're a
pretty little thing
Well aren't you？
Uh，thank you
I think
And you're convinced that the entire world revolves around you
am I right？
Going through life thinking that there's nothing you can't have
It must be
very pleasant
I'm sorry
what are you
trying to say？
I'm confused
who are
you exactly？
I have this tiny
little birthmark on my inner thigh
He used to kiss it
How he used to
love kissing me there
Dr Tenma，that is
You know him？
Oh no
See？See？
She left
because you were late
and it's all
because you had to stop in that store
Oh，too bad
I'm sorry
about that
Can you do me a
favour and apologise for me？
Wait，hey，Tenma
Maybe if you give
her a call right now
she might
come back
Who knows？
I want to stop by
the hospital for a quick minute
What？At this hour？
Ah，I've had
it with you
Fine，leave
Kenzo，你係我…
你係我嘅全部
Mr， Junger's，請等我
Mr， Junger's
Kenzo，發生咩事啊？
Wait，Kenzo
I have to
talk to you
Mr， Yunker's
Kenzo
please just wait
Kenzo？
Oh，great
I broke my heel
Kenzou
健仔
I saw him
you know
Oh yes
a year ago
in Dusseldorf
I saw him
It was Johann
I'm sure of it
你殺咗約翰，嗬？
Guess I'll…
Have to kill you